################################################################################
How did viewing a diff between two versions of a file help you see the bug that
was introduced?
> Makes it easy to see what's changed.

How could having easy access to the entire history of a file make you a more
efficient programmer in the long term?
> You can see what you've changed and how your code has evolved.

What do you think are the pros and cons of manually choosing when to create a
commit, like you do in Git, vs having versions automatically saved, like Google
docs does?
> Manually commit/save:
 * Pros
   * Can easily discard changes if don't want
   * Let's you decide best time to save
   * Let's you save changes at logical points
 * Cons
   * Can lose work if computer crashes or has a failure
   * May go too long between saving and not be able to easily see what's
     changed
> Auto-commit/save:
 * Pros
   * Always up to date
   * Losing data because of failure less likely
 * Cons
   * May save things you don't want
   * History may not exist or may be much less useful

Why do you think some version control systems, like Git, allow saving multiple
files in one commit, while others, like Google Docs, treat each file separately?
> Git sees things as part of a project whereas Google Docs really only
  understands invidual files.  Some things are inherently related such as
  multiple source files in a programming project or a HTML file and related
  CSS file.

How can you use the commands git log and git diff to view the history of files?
> git log allows you to see the commit history for a file.  git diff allows
  you to see what's changed between commits

How might using version control make you more confident to make changes that
could break something?
> Because its easy/easier to revert.

Now that you have your workspace set up, what do you want to try using Git for?
> Scripting!

